Mission to crash out
Ghost already did he took the whole crowd
That's how you know the haunts alive
Lights flicker chats in the right
And somewhere gold's about to die
Heroes are loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghosts just grin
Let's fucking go
And now we're flying
He's chaos
With the halo wild but true
Help me down, sky lost
It was report may I have permission to crash
Thank you. Let's kill the tour
Psyche is proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud
I don't know if I saw
This one's gonna look good
Cracked out, cracked out
We had stories
He did stories
I'm guessing it's B though, right?
down
beautiful
look beautiful
by the way. That's the one that's on the view. Yeah, that's top three. That's top three.
At least top three. I agree. Yeah. Maybe top two. No, the number one is me and the page
on the Alex. That one. I'm going to take a lot of that one down. Number two is thank
I am proud of that, this one.
And I was able to actually put it together
in a pretty,
I just, it just all came together perfectly.
So-
Oh, what a beautiful fucking song.
Yeah, that was awesome.
Thank you very much.
I was getting tired of the Thank You Go song,
but this one, I'll tell you what, beautiful song.
Yeah, and okay, I went over to beat us to like maybe like give her a
We all went over to beat us if you didn't know that we just came back from beat us all three of us
I went over there like you know, maybe give her a giggle because remember when I wore my speedos like you know
And she like laughed and then we kind of like so I thought she'd laugh
they're jealous, they're butthurt, they're jelly
they are
it's just me ghost in sight, you know how bad they want to be up here?
she's up there with fucking blogger and thing that is
they all want to be here at the cool kids table
yeah, well
You know, yeah, you know, oh, it's opi is Hannah. Well, you know what opi me Alex is like I'm gonna have to know
Because Hannah was saying things about oh
She said oh psyche munches on fleas like, you know, he's like just like
Oh, I'm I wouldn't be surprised to have it is blocked. I don't know. I
Yes, you call me cycle
Oh, you shouldn't have left assets line. Did you hear be there though? By the way, ghost anybody noticed that the voice patch was on form
fucking mode
You hear what
I heard she was crying
She was crying literally crying by the way, and they were they were they were saying ghost get out of here
They were picking on you for some of you
The dubs the guy was a dick
You're just like fucking like oh my god, and the Chris what it was Christine getting my business
Jesus oh, it's summer was up there. That's right
Wait summer did just go up and go at beta. Oh you missed it again sake
it's fucking me that we don't quite can feed us
Well, okay, I'm poor mom. He's a nice person
Don't let me start it pal. I found my calling
CB CB my man
Yeah, Mickey Mouse that bitch is fucking voice boxers have full effect and I she had it on fucking
One or two or whatever it was not listen to be tomorrow, bro
And listen to right now
I'm beat a mouse and tomorrow like hey, I'm beater
Hey
And it's tomorrow
Crazy
TV says garrus cool, I don't think he's cool, but
And Brina was actually being pretty cool tonight
Who is
And Bruno of all people Bruno Bruno was being cool brain of all people. Yeah, it's always cool, bro
If you have a problem with Bruno, you have a problem with life, you know what I'm saying
Bruno's the epitome of just some
fat mobster go good like
Let me show you know
Bruno is being really cool today. I'll give you that
He's always cool, man. Bruno's the buzz
And they were right Bruno when Bruno came in here. He was all like came in and scared. I used to white night Bruno every night
Oh, and you got the white as well sober a white night is as every night broke a little my boy. I used to come in
Right
Yes, my friend ten minutes. We need a five hour donation. Yes, my friend. My
My fine fellow friend
let's do it
It was great. We played again actually because that's a new song. Can we just get another?
Yeah, that was great. Let's play it again. Let's play it again, Sam. Good one
Permission to crush out
Ghost already did he took the whole crowd
That goes through the night
That's how you know, the haunts are live
Lights flicker, chats in the ride
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes in loud, like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghosts just grin
I chose you
No
Ha, dumb dumb, I can't believe it, I like it, I like it, but it makes it sound good bro, only I can do that.
Oh my god, I just caught that.
But he took a sneak watch and fell around because he scores, you heard?
Oh my god.
Oh, I'm gonna cry.
Beautiful fall.
Yayyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy
I picked your ghost dancer right now doing the pants and footwork
I'm finna put you on the shot, yaaay
No, please
Alice, write the song
YAYYYY
Oh, I like it
Somebody gave $5
Go
That's a good one man
And blogger over to give you $5
You're just making me song psych because we're gonna knock down though I'll send a page song off soon
You getting better and better sir very beautiful song yes, I think your lecture song that's awesome
Like your spark of flame something about her being awesome. That's wrong by the least like somebody might have said $5
Arbiter send them $5, but yeah fuck Arbiter. He's a bitch
Thank you Arbiter. Thank you Arbiter in the chat. I love you
It's a beautiful fucking song.
Arbiter, you don't have a cell.
Cell the man.
So he doesn't have to wait a month.
I don't know.
He's Canadian.
No, he's not Canadian.
Arbiter's Canadian.
Who the fuck's Canadian?
Easy.
I thought he was was like it thought it's something about they're all Canadian, yeah, I'm from West Virginia
It's a W
Yeah, but I'm from Colombia, I'm not in Colombia. You're from West Virginia. You're saying you live in West Virginia
Oh
May I have permission to
Can I crash out? Yes, you may but you know what? It's like what we're gonna say
Where I don't understand like vloggers over there being like pretty annoying like he's like he's like just the way he talks is annoying like
I agree his whole assistance is annoying. Everything is there and his whole face everything about him is annoying
I was trying to be funny and then he's like I was like, you know kind of put I don't have a problem with vegan patriot
I know I don't but then he's like why are you making fun of vegan patriot because of the wig on I was like
I
Can't be funny anymore because they hate us and that know the woman Victoria. They do they do bro
trust me man, you have to like
You understand they're still there
And only
You know my problem is Alice. I gave psyche money
I know
That's why they were doing what they were doing to you goes because they they wanted to like feel like yo
You give psyche hundreds of dollars like we're gonna play you
That's why
He made a good point
Summer did join
so you're a good friend to psyche and you actually donate their natural friends and they don't donate
so now that they have you up there it's like a feeding frenzy like this attack this piece of
shit that thinks he's better than us i mean i give it to them i didn't argue man because i
Okay, um Vicky nobody wants a free lap dance. I don't have permission to crash
Real
Were you asleep last night yes or no
You disappeared for like an hour and a half you had you you had your mic
What's up? I
Took I love you. I love you big here. I'm just teasing. I'm just teasing a little bit. I was wiki get it up here, baby
He's CB
She poor woman. Let's say she showed me her tits and she had CB. Oh CB. Yeah, that's a girl. Yeah
After that was author for a second
Godi's kind of friend and like but they kind of like, you know, and then she was like
All right, so let her up and then kill the life
But that's awesome
No, we can't dig we cannot
You selfish asshole, I
Was shocked when I saw them are they nice kids? She's bad. Is she beautiful talk to me?
Big
The big so she like
She was such a nice mild manner lady and then all of a sudden she was like backstage
Like literally like last oh wait, so it's the it's the Natalie lady. No, no, no, no
It's um, it's one of gaudy's friends and she's like kind of looks like she's like
From Iowa or something, you know, she's kind of like
She looks like she's from Iowa. That's the funniest thing I've ever heard
You must be from Idaho like you got that know that I don't know it's like why are you?
Iowa
I mean from I don't know but she doesn't get through these past year kind of more, you know talk to her kind of a little bit on TikTok and stuff
She's not me talk to her
Um Vicky do you know how old is she she good-looking will you throw her a bang will you throw her one day if she were so
Alex you have to I think that she's probably like doesn't want to
you to be
a
of the
Come on. That's not even a timeout. That's a hide. She formed on me without even me kicking up kicking JT from the chat
She was can she perform on me?
Jesus
They're actually they're like, what are they called? No, but DJ Electra formed on this last night, man
And she laughed about it. Well, he's not you know, you can't go shit. Fuck that. You ha ha ha
Evil
I don't think she meant it in a mean way. I think she
Hope not man. I don't know. I don't know. What if she did?
Why did tigger look on the toilet? He was looking for she poured mom. I don't get focused in mean way or not
Did she pour mom?
It's um, I don't know. She just made fun of it really evil after it, you know, like what a rich funny
Almost like she had the joke ready
Like she almost like she does it all the time
You know, like she had that shit ready like at least now, you know, you can get the shit fucked out of you
Haha, like what and it was literally a cock pumping shit out of an asshole
That was the poor mom
She came out with that joke after like come on brothers and pick an FBI agent to take a shit out
That woman Hannah Hannah was just
She was like, you know, she kept saying oh, can I be a mod in your chat because I'm gonna get kicked off by God
You know, no, nobody asked for much should be never be a mod. No, no
You hear that just immediately banned them kick them like hey, how's this from odd?
Cakes helping on fleas and
Singles
I like it
She does have medical problems that but uh, you know, and like, you know, if she did have the big C
It's not a joke to me or anything, but she was just she would you come at me rude?
I'm gonna come back as you like just as hard like you can't like and she didn't know is like within her chat watching and she's like
These all day, I'm like eat my fleas bitch
I know I will I mean I'm I'm I'm I'm sassy now you know
That's his car. They don't don't tell me sassy scarlet sassy scarlet is like well, I don't know
reality Nancy he man
I mean you guys like you got quite the gems up here, man. You're a lot of features up here, bro
whoo, thank God for James Cowboys
I love I love the people here, but sometimes they like I noticed they turn on the other chats not not not all of them
But not Jamie not Jamie. No, not Jamie. I'm talking about, you know
Don't you ever say something about Jamie? I'll turn into Joe Shipley. Don't you know Joe Shipley gets pissed?
Like don't talk about my beat. Uh, like I'll don't make me turn into Shipley
Don't say no bad about my
You've been doing
Years like I'm really you're not like off the turnip truck. I mean
And I'm not no offense beta, but I literally I did shit with you. Oh, no, no you started
She was a little bit like she's like, oh psyche didn't even come up here to like talk to me
Um, yes, I did wait. Yeah, I came up there to talk to blogger and
Whoever the fuck else was exactly. Hello. No Victoria Jim never talk. I just said it was Victoria Jay here
And then she's like, I gotta go
Who knows Victoria Jane anyway? I heard you say that earlier. Who is that?
Weirdo from IP to that is like she's never on camera. She uses she sounds like she's like 500 pounds
But she uses that cute little avatar face. Oh like what come only?
Well, I don't know
Yeah, but yeah
Talking to blogger like oh blogger you yell at your mom and she's fucking yelling her mom all night
She her mom will get the next room in her house and stuff and she sounds like I mean
No one
It's gonna get mad at us cuz she's been like making videos so blogger and all these people are weak
And we're like kind of hanging out with them on like
Like is she gonna come back and like
Understand
What's going on, you know, she gets
Like blogger is like he was making fun of his nostrils. She said his nostrils have gotten bigger
It's where the guy
She made a whole live about blogger. He was talking about his nostrils like them. She's got bigger my man
I
Just like I think the problem Alexander had is that she doesn't want me to like
Make her be friends with beta or like no try to get to be friends. Okay, so are you literally just best friends with Alex?
Alexander sorry
Alexander yeah, and it's like so I'm not gonna push but and then it's like but you know
I'm on a 30-day like no contact
Alexander
It's yeah, but so but so all respect her boundaries. I don't want to bother her
She's not gonna make it bro. I told her last night
I told you and then I went there and I told her I was like I was to the Sykes
I told him that you're not gonna make it and she was like, I'm glad you're here and I don't know some shit
And then I was like, I'm gonna go back to Sykes now. I'm telling you that you're crying
You're crying hysterical and you can't get out of bed. That's what I told her
I was like, I'm gonna tell Sykes you're crying and you can't get out of bed because you miss him so much
And she was like, no, don't tell him that Alex
I swear I was like, I'm kidding. I'm kidding. I'm gonna tell him that
But he misses you. I told him. I'm like, yo, I just said like Alex and the first things out of his mouth was I miss her
Because you did and you said that
He misses you and I was like he also misses beta I had to throw that in there too like
You were there earlier they all thought the ghost your psyche boy you gave him a lot of money
You guys are putting psyche in a tough spot right now man. It's to be a fives though unlike each other
And then she went on some rent
of the
the
I feel like I mean you make enough money brother
that I he saw me on a on a show like five years ago, and I didn't know anything about tarot and he
Can't he can't find the episode and then he's like, oh well you you did a show about Bronzeberg
So I'm going back on the bet that you know about finding and so
That's just a bullshit. So you owe me exiled one of your burning
No, you're never gonna come on the panel yet. I didn't have a month today
But he just had a bunch of shit to talk. Yeah, we just gotta give him to Alexandra. She's like oh
She's like a war machine. She's just like chew these people up like docks them like completely like all you gotta do is give her the name
But here you go, and you'll make a whole fucking live about it the next day
You are her son the worst like you don't hear some lowers now like
How can you be firms with somebody like psych?
Yeah, they went crazy pretty much they can't take it
I think that they're
Maybe like they're like well why can't
you know, like I think that they want you know, I think they want to get donations and it's like they
I wish I had a ghost what a psyche have a ghost that gives them
100 and 50s and 20s here and there why I want that what the fuck fuck psyche, right?
It's just fuck ghost
The one right have that that's all it is like me. I would see hatred. Don't you're fighting boy. Oh, no
You didn't put the L in there in there a gossiper. That's why I hate that shit. Yeah, um, you know, you're fighting boy
You know, there's no
I don't have
Many donators, but I have like a few very very generous ones that have kept me. I wouldn't be able to
Meet at the new you mean may
the
Shout out to your new mic shout out to your new computer. I'm good. I really gave it to you by the way
Yes
And it's like and they talk shit like your psyche boy. Okay. They say like, oh, you gave all this
I can do whatever the fuck I want with my money
Right, and you know and also I do want to say guys. I do really support
Summer and it's like and I'm a member of summer
I guess whatever she's okay
Is like really like she's honest because she could have just like taken Christine side and the girls club kind of thing
We're like, oh, you know, I love summer man. She wasn't agreeing. She was like
I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I was going to say, I
You know, some are like fucking was like take my red
I'm known for
Alex didn't say you're psyching boys. Thank you boys. So and yeah, we are
They just upset one of their boys. I'm gonna change my membership to like like Alexandra said the psyche's Alexander the way you say it bro
It's weird. Yeah, that was kind of no, but he always says it that way like he's
That's how she pronounces her name how how does she pronounce it Alexandra?
The same, you know if I was gay might take my head hard when I hear Alexander
I
Doxing Queen yeah, God bless her bro. She's every doctor's worst nightmare
Didn't abandon him
I mean, it's like I feel like
You know be it is has been like out there. She's a host of a show and it's like my I don't know everyone
Who's like gonna have a show?
And her name's been out there before she said it before. I mean, I don't know. It's like not you can't lose Alexandra over beta though
Come on, man
I'm not saying loser or were but you still have to show her like as much attention as you do to be the
About you promote you. She was so
Secure we can say by his book. Oh, I look like she might have met you like
Don't forget about her is all I'm saying
No, of course not. I'm counting the days till till I'm
Yeah, but she's but I think that she took something the wrong way of like she's like, oh you're just gonna defend B to the death
Yeah, exactly. She doesn't want to get in the way of it, bro
It's not she doesn't want to be in the middle of your and Beatles relationship
She understands that that relationship has been long before she was around like she gets it now
She's not so upset you brought her into it
I don't like that mustafabi shit, though, man.
I know well, you know, it's like it's a little bit controversial, but then I have like, you know, I have that song
But these you to write your public figure everyone is so you know for grabs
That's why man. Don't come up. It looks I mean, I I had to just
Because it was like there's just so much going on with the other people trying to dox me
So I just dox myself and then I told my family
Hey, I'm on YouTube
There's really money you to get ready for a new one
Yeah, I'm on YouTube get ready. I'm on YouTube get ready for a new one daily a lot of pizzas are coming
And some scrap metal dudes
Yeah, I can deal with the scrap metal people I can deal with the pizzas I can deal with the manure
It's like, you know what it's like, but it's like really like nobody else has anything to do with it
So I I'm really about just sticking the individuals. I think it's like really easy man
It's also really out of bounds even to do that shit. They're putting their first of all they're saying that oh your dad
I just talked to your dad.
My dad passed away last year.
And so I don't want to hear like,
oh, I just talked to your dad.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, and they're like, oh, I don't want to talk to,
you know, they're like, oh, he said his name is,
or he said your name is Alexander Bates or something.
And I was like, oh my gosh, I don't mean.
I can't it's just crazy. Hey, Jamie's and I and then Katie in that chat just terrible
I mean, it's like I'm sorry Jamie. I try to tell her I told Katie. I was like, hey, I was like, I was like call Jamie
Like what are you doing? Does that have a heart or something? She's uh, you know, she she's she wants to talk to you
And she just ignored me when I
Say she called you are normal
Tell me Norman Bates. Well, that's yeah, yeah Norman Bates is my favorite movie psycho, you know
My favorite movies in the world Albert Hitchcock classic movie one of the best base motel
What's the movie son birds
No doubt. Well, that was the birds, but psycho is another one. Yeah, movies. Yeah
Birds is a trippy movie because it's about this woman that like goes to an island
You know to visit her boyfriend or something and then she brings over like a bird
She brings a bird
or it's because of the birds you brought, but all the birds are going crazy on the island, so it's because of the birds going cool.
Well listen, sir, if those birds, if you watch that movie, you're going to be freaked out about birds for at least a month.
Jamie's con boys, hit the link so I can hear your beautiful voice.
Jamie, I'm so Jamie doing tonight.
And they melt my heart they pull on my heart strings with the little hearts and stuff
By the way, I really had no problem with
I said, I apologize. I really didn't give a fuck. It's not a big deal. You think that is?
Yeah, do you see what I did to the poor man? I really don't need him, but
Well, he's kind of like getting in the middle. He was like getting in the talking. Oh, well, you know
He was getting them talking about listen. I told him this is this is what I told him
You know what the fuck you're talking about, sir. You might
Set there and shut the fuck up
Okay, I mean it's like don't throw shade at me
I would say and your mares is crazy though. She just took it in rain
You know your mom come in the room the next day was a two-hour movie like see that is this in Canada with his mom
You should observe like I mean there's something to what she said about like he is kind of like
and then it's like a very intense energy.
I feel it, I feel it, and I feel like he does have
an influence without him even maybe knowing.
Well listen, the only thing he has, let me talk real quick.
The only thing he has an influence on is like trivia.
What's his grade?
I love trivia night.
Well maybe with people like Joe.
But when you sit there and like talk shit about
the big guns, I mean, you know what's gonna happen.
Obviously I'm gonna fuck you up.
Shut there and shut the fuck up
Well, I'm just saying like, you know, I wrote a song about him too and the song is you know
I'm pretty complimentary. Yeah, I don't give a fuck about the community song
Let me just look like
No, I think I was think that wasn't someone said it
Listen hey time if you don't know
Well listen listen listen if you don't know fuck you're talking about just shut the fuck up
We talking to fat boys
I know but people are always want to get their opinion. Are you calling me still before you don't boy?
Yeah, I get to fucking punch
You know push your little belly and you go. Hey, hey, hey, that's a close one. Don't want I'm ghosting
I'm the mention one man. You're a couple fucking hundred of dollars will probably fall out of your ass
And
It's a tomorrow is the you know YouTube payday. Hey, what's up time?
September so it's so it's YouTube pays like for like
Cash app or anything she would only accept super chats because she thought it helped the algorithm because YouTube benefits and so she thought
it's also you know it's also good
which has generated a lot of excitement
give it back
I love you ghost
well you have a month to give it back
because he's not going to get it for a month
take all that money you gave him
he's not going to see it for a month
he's gonna be hungry
He's gonna have to pay bills and that money's just gonna be in limbo for a month
Bow and only 50% of it is gonna come in in a month
That's true
Think about that. Does that make sense in our world?
But you know what it's fine because they they they're in it they're in it with me
They're making money. I'm making money. Everyone's happy, right? It's like it's like
Well, I think the people that aren't making YouTube money. They kind of have this play
Strike and stuff because I have never I don't get I haven't had a strike in
Like a long long long time and it's like I'm gonna strike you channel. Oh, please go suck it
I
You know you sound like Joanie when you laugh right there that's not like Joanie is a wild one
I love Joanie. Did you hear laughing last night? Like just romantic Joanie
It's just not like a retard
Yeah, yeah. Oh, she I mean she's laughed like that where she like she laughs when she thought about how I
She's like talking
Two things to listen to I do love a I do love a you know, and also like
You know, she like I connected with
You know, I can't do with her a long time ago. I'm Alex and then like we had a little falling out because
I had told Elisa about something like that you know Johnny before Lisa you guys were friends
I met her on a Lisa's show and stuff and then in her discord and then like she would send me like
the hubus dank song hey there she is there she is
Here we go
The Hoopa Stank song and and yeah, we're back guys.
Well, every time I see Ribs, I think of Joni because she just send Ribs to Lisa every night.
I think
I think she might be
For me, she's very fucking beautiful. Maybe Joanie and girls. That's all good
Yeah, we're all good
Fucking and she just laughs like that. What you fuck her. I think like how
The reason I met a Lisa in the first place
So I can meet Joni because like
No, don't lie don't lie you don't care about Joni. Oh, you want to listen to me?
Don't talk to me
Where's Elisa anyway? What happened in that cycle? Where is she?
She was on the other night and like I said I donated
I sent a song that I wrote
You donated?
And then she just didn't even acknowledge me at all
She didn't say my name
Hey thank you she didn't
Yeah, I wish it don't think she thinks she's too big time but I go on is
A phone call or something she's talking some guy on the phone that she probably like oh, so you okay
I just want her to hear the song but she didn't obviously care about
You know why you know she might like the girl song
Well, I don't I don't know
Fucking Russian who is that guy she beat up that I gave her like $10 million a week
Yeah, you think she's a fuck about us on our five-hour song come on, bro
She like heard like
Not not like me and stuff, and then it's like she kind of I don't know if she just like
Lump in a crash out because sometimes there wasn't even that way in the song
Okay, what's wrong ghost? I'm not looking. I'm not gonna bring it. I'm sorry. I am crashing now
I just want you to play the ghost song again. Here we go. I'm assuming Johnny will be up here if there was a link
Oh my god
Who's the guy who beat up all those names?
Aro?
Bro!
YEPAAA
Beautiful
What?
That's how you know, the horns alive, lights flicker, chats in the ride, and somewhere goes about to die
Was that a BMW with wings like that?
Hahahaha
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes, keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling, the trolls start crying, ghosts just grin
Let's fucking go, and now we're flying, he's chaos
That was fucking beautiful
Yeah!
See my crush out!
Oh!
That's it
Psyche is proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud proud
You're moving your ass full? I'm dancing. I'm shaking my apples though. My pelvis like Elvis.
I'm trying to get down. What's this called?
I'm doing a terpia.
No!
Beautiful.
1, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6, 7, 8, 6
It comes to dream
Don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't
No
That's awesome
Beautiful soft love it. Good job. Thank you so much
Top three is top three my man. That's top two
Tell you what I'm in the clouds
But you say a little beaters live right now. It's think that is be the pages of their prairie page
My little page
Yeah
I mean swing by the same
That's kind of mean to say that
We country goes right whatever bro people can do whatever they want. No, I'm sure
Well, you know Ivana punch you when I
Their video, you know, but the other person and she said well that doesn't look like that person at all
And I was like then I it's blogger license. I said there's an artistic license. I I mean
I want to throw up man
It kept saying oh, this is ghost here and it's like all these different people
I was like, what the hell you know what Alex you should go to be the same
Blockers there and pages there pages and blockers vicinity that alone
She's cool screen page look at her. She's showing a little kitty cat
And she looks all hot too and cute look at page
the
that is a bugging
It's okay. You guys are still there, man. I think that is scratching his bull head now that he shaved
Talking
Give me permission, brother
It's another girl she sounds like she's 90
Please ghost please go and fuck them off please I'm watching
Like somebody has to go and fuck them up. Do you know me pal because I can't take it much longer
No, shit, I told you
You both go up there. Just leave me here alone dwelling. I'll go there
But you guys gonna promise me like you're not gonna judge me and it is you guys are gonna watch
My god, they've been AI of me
They have AI all these AI videos of me that's so cool. Thank you for making AI of me
Are we watching the same thing no where is the AI?
Okay five minutes so get out of here. Oh
No, listen to this. Oh, I see it. I see it
Is that Chris K? Who the fuck's there?
According to the Canadians on the jail, I can't show people.
I never fucked any of that.
Of course, it's gonna go there and fuck their shit up.
Okay.
You just want to look.
Oh my gosh, he left. Paige left.
I don't know how funny I am.
Bring me down to like a more like a more like tolerable level is that what you'd like to do as a Canadian
Coast is there
Cyclops is there the little fuck way
Is he on the panel yeah, he's on the bottom
Hey man, I hear you were shit talking to me somewhere tonight.
That thing that is smile is something off with it man, he's just like, that smile.
You said it.
I said blogger
I can't believe page ran as soon as schools came on I mean
I value, I value people that know how to be like comedic and they know how to be funny, which I, I do, I do have a good sense of humor and all that shit, like I said, it's circumstance because it just came off this huge blow up where it really seemed like your, your mood changed. Okay.
Like, I honestly.
I can't hear you.
I apologize.
Thank you.
Shut up, ghosts.
I don't hate you.
Back.
Yeah.
That's all.
It's not that serious.
It wasn't that serious.
Oh, she came back.
Do you care that she hasn't come up here to say hello to you?
She was here the other night.
This is fine. She came over to us.
I know, but still, what the fuck?
I apologize to you, ghost.
Hey, what are you talking about, ma'am?
Ghost, you're going to camp up or what?
He said you're going to camp up again.
You did already?
No, I'm not.
He's gonna come up
No, he doesn't come up when you ask him he's not gonna come up
Run it baby
Yep
and longer chat
because you blew up at pace the other night. Oh no.
Can I apologize?
Yeah. Yeah. Can I apologize? Sure. Let me take this party out of my beautiful morning to apologize.
Oh
Let's kick ghosts off the panel
He's a bitch
No
She wouldn't backstage until you apologize to think about power trip. I love when she gets on this power trip shit
That's her way of saying like you don't don't need to me backstage
Well, we're having a good time.
Thank you, everybody.
Who is Jill Scotty?
That Chinese fuck some like Chinese fuck that's always up there once they're blue they do not like them
That's some weird dude, bro
Look at pre-page man
Ghost just kidnap page and get back here pal
Yeah, that's the only mission right now. Okay, so fuck off. Get paged and get over here
That was easy oh my god
He blew hammer he blew hammer is and be this chat now
Isn't that your boy he blew him
You
Darrell Cortez is there Darrell. You're the right that guy with the hood. Oh
My gosh
Mom
the
The little shock face is out of the shock
Very page you see the shock faces that site you remember him page
Who nights ago
Hey fam
Come by but she didn't but it's okay. I'm sorry. She's a beat us with things that isn't blogger
No, it's not okay, man. It's okay in your book
And it's like yeah, she's I know she's trivia and stuff. Maybe I don't plan a trivia
I guess now. Let's stop playing trivia. See if they come over here
It's true United cities
the
he'd listen to alex are you a man's advice
it's like an AI photo of him like sitting in like in like at his house
yeah yeah
it's pretty funny
hilarious
that was my foresight
I did on accident I didn't know she
you know though when I came at him like you live with your mom and all that shit the next day she ran with it
She made a whole movie about it like now. I know you're 58 and live with your mom and cat
I was like fuck and then she threw me up there like I didn't expose you as I'm a queen did I said my queen
She made a whole thing about it. I love her
She's so funny and she's really cute man
Don't lose Alexandria mayors over this shit. I don't know fuck. I really do hope to be able to
Well, you have to you gotta keep her. I mean come on
Friends with her and beat it just I'm very very you can pull it all just hang out with be though
on your own, you know, on certain days and how was I was on your own on certain days like you didn't do it
I can I can I gotta keep that berated
Exactly
I love both, you know, who's just friends. You don't like each other. Okay. I'll see you on Saturday. I'll see you on Monday like
I
Can share custody of me
Exactly you get it pal you get psyche Monday Tuesdays Wednesdays you get them Thursday Friday Saturdays. All right, I'm relax and
Fucking the ghost is the daddy does sugar daddy. Just donating
I could care my psyche here's a hundred
the
It's just weird what 90 humans
Just 200 people that sounds no 90 90. Okay, that's about right. I
Was like 200 that's that's pretty crazy
You have dirty that's 90 in our book
She always has you know like about a hundred people, but then she's like oh well
He's like you only come on my show when there's a hundred people in the chat
I don't ever look at the numbers like when there's a nap bro. What 90 humans?
Find that entertaining. I guess I guess so I mean she built it up
It's like a brand right you've been around a couple years. You just like build up or clientele like any other business
Um, yeah, no shit that's that's why she has 90 actually because that's all it is is drama
They just waiting for her to start crying
Right like yeah be just crying again
Bro drama sales in this bitch in this YouTube world man
They do not want to hear fucking talk about fucking
Trump in the Middle East they want to hear fucking
Doxing and who's fucking who and crying and clumsy did this in the Alexandria
Fucked Alexander McQueen and psyche fucking eats
Fish tacos. They just want to hear crazy shit because life is boring bro, right? It's like a sofa, bro
He was just one entertainment. They want to like forget about reality
they don't want to come home and watch the same boring shit they can watch on Fox 5
like Trump, the Middle East, what do you think about that? They don't want that
they went out of the box, holy shit, SpongeBob shit
so to break
Anybody asked for the link in the chat. I'm sorry. I'm making a ball. They're all asking for the link
I Johnny's crying for the link. God. He's crying. I think I'm so fucking ass in school of Athens
I think the other ghost of Athens. Oh, come on, Johnny. Come get up here. Hey, don't be depressed my my little Jonah native
Are you the press?
You know what you got you are so right about that woman Hannah. She is a nightmare. She's her to saying oh
I munch on fleas. I'm the psycho that munches on these and stuff and you're so right about her
I mean she was what a cunt
What a way to be greeted on a god did you hear that I munch on fleas what a cunt
Talking about Hannah you finally saw her for what kind of combat
Yeah, she said I munch on fleas and I'm psycho and she was just talking to you know
I was looking at reading the chat and stuff took you along. All right. I see a cat. I see a cat
God I don't know why I see your avatar on the phone, but on TV. It's the nipples the white thing
It's still the nipple Alexander
Good update your shit happens. What's happening, man?
the
It's not what I changed it to though. That's what's in like what you're saying. It's different. You can't see shit on one side
I got you can see I can see you have oh now it's back to the accents thing that's like school at this picture the ref I else anything
Yeah, yep
I'm sorry. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I donated because you wouldn't give us the link Goddy and I would tell and you'll give us the link
So everyone was like, oh, you don't psyche won't let anybody up unless you pay. So I paid $2
Let me troll let me troll a little here
Alex, you know that that I know that that's not true, but I like to make psyche think it's true. Yeah
Did you send them? Oh, yeah, you did. Thank you. Yes. I gave a dollar for me and a dollar from God, so we can come up
Thank you. That's you my man. I got you, bro. Good work. Yeah
That was nice of you though, I will say
For me and the dollar from God. Okay, whatever. It's better. That was nice of you. I've seen you donate some shit before
Yeah, I don't know how you see it because I actually sell it to him
You know what sell is that's the difference. That's the difference. You don't need to be told. Oh good job
You gave money like ghost. He needs to be he wants to see his name up there, you know
That's what I was talking earlier, bro, like I know
I'm happy to I'm happy to oblige, you know, for special requests and stuff like that. It's not like
Okay, psyche listen to this right
Likey from us from a psychological point of view right somebody donates something to somebody
There's two reasons they're either doing it because they want to help that person
Or they're doing it to make themselves feel better about themselves now. They're trying to manipulate those two
Correct. Oh, yeah, I could be but but still the point is is if they're trying to manipulate him
That's not for that person's best interest, right? So let's go with either your best interest or the other person's
Ghost was told
But listen, let me finish. I'm gonna lean in 25 seconds
Be comfortable that he can be he can run some things. He doesn't want to start his own show
All right, but listen psyche. He was told flat-out. What goes goes to his told flat-out
Do you want to help psyche out the most you can? Yes, I do want to okay
if you said the cash app he will get more money alex pointed that out before
how much
uh...
you can't talk to him he doesn't have cash app
and it's like it's kind of like
it's like i don't know
i'm not gonna like
fuck doesn't have cash
he's lying
psyche psyche so he told you he doesn't have cash app and you just believe it
he's a gamer psyche they all have cash up
he's fucking got cash app he just needs his name
i don't know guys i'm not gonna turn against those
everyone has to send it i think i think that is good to get
yeah no we don't know that
because I didn't know that as well I used to donate to TPP and Eli all the time with super chats and stickers and
Then people started telling me like you Alex like stop like you're wasting your money YouTube takes half of it
You know so the island that way maybe
Alex if you just listen to what I said
You didn't listen to me. I flat out explained that goes to his told, you know, he was asked
Do you want to help him out as best you can? And he said yes and then was explained to
I love it when it's like you get so crazy like this. It's stuttered. It's okay ghost isn't gonna stop donating you realize that right?
What the hell is ghost?
What happened?
He's a dumb dumb that guy
I'm happy with it. Go see come back
However, they want a psyche listen to psyche. He's getting all crazy here. I'm gonna start stuttering like this
No, my favorite one. He gets pissed at me. Alex. Alex. No, no, Alex when he gets mad at you. That's funny. Yeah, that's come on
That's the best
He's getting complimented he thinks he's getting attacked, you know, I love the psyches. He's so cute
I got a strong jaw to psyche nice looking jaw
You're welcome. See now back on his good side. You see how easy that's all it takes
Compliment
Where's Mason the drummer, man, I I smell mason
Last night Mason had a quite a day as today, you know, I have the record for number of wrenches. Do you know that got him?
Johnny get up here with a number of wrenches. We need a girl up here. We need a woman up here
Yeah
Number of wrenches given and then taken away by psyche. I'm almost up to double digits. He's given no
There's no way you beat me
You know I got you beat I got you beat because he doesn't
That's a compliment that's a compliment to you though because he's scared sometimes to take away your wrench
You need a wrench to me you'll be like fucking school. I don't care if you don't come back. I'm taking that shit away
30 bucks tonight because he um he privacy but thank you that wasn't I wasn't
I was saying that you took my wrench away more times than Tony
Get up here, baby
Alex and I are alike you like before I heard Alex say don't give me a wrench yet because I'm the same way like
I don't want you to give me that shit yet. You know that needs a good time, bro
Those are the devil's rings
People get so funny with wrenches. No, that's like the game. Maybe
People treat that shit like gold the next one is
It turns purple and and yeah, it's a cat's eye and then this one's a pentagram. Oh, that's what the cat's eye is
That's for the devil
Wait, go back to the cat's eye
Cat's eye the middle one. Yeah, see it
Well, I heard devil
I heard the devil and he said go back to the cat. I don't I want to know the cat's eye looks like
Well, I think
Wrench Manch exactly Johnny Wrench Manch
The evil eye I know the evil eye got you you know the Turkish evil eye. Yeah, it's evil eye. Yep
Yeah, that's cool
I know a lot of people get it and they don't know what it means either. Oh, yeah, I was in Greece
Man, I got your rent ready, right Johnny if you were telling him you grab your nuts
I got your fucking rent ready. Oh, dude. I was doing it when you said it actually
I was like I was holding my shit before I
Yo, you missed a joke about the three kids and they're all talking about you know what they're getting for Christmas
It's an Indian kid a Spanish kid and Italian kid and the Indian kid is like oh my goodness
I know what I'm getting. I'm getting the remote control car. I
Looked under the bed and I found it. Oh, I know what I'm getting for Christmas
And then the Spanish kid was like, oh, I know what I'm getting to I'm getting that fucking racetrack
I always wanted, you know, I found it in the closet
And then the tank it was like oh, yeah, well, I'm getting the bicycle. I was wanting to do the carino
Because I was my dad
I asked my dad
Was my bicycle and he said
No, no, he actually said the bike I want for Christmas is in my dad's pants
That's what the kids said and they're like what do you mean?
And he's like yeah, because then when I asked my dad was my bike. He said I got your fucking bike ready
I
Yeah, I got you
The movie Don Juan you ever see the movie Don Juan remember I showed you the scene from it
Don Juan
I
Let's bow down for a second
Yeah, but that's the movies got the joke in it down
Cupcake
I know where you know
Joseph Gordon Levitt
Johnny loves hockey
No, she loves
Tony Danza
Somebody told me really bad tonight who who was it give me a name it was a I don't know the name they caught they they caught they made
They made a donation
Wait, I'm speaking. I'm partying the Red Sea
I feel better that there's a woman up here right now
Oh, wow. Thank you. Oh, God. Look who it is.
I didn't see you. Hey, me, girl.
Okay. No, she's not.
Yes, she is.
So you're lucky.
Hey, bro, I don't know what the fuck.
You're joining it next to me.
God, I don't think I deserve this.
We kind of paid a little while.
a puddle of sand
Jamie thank you
Too much
exactly
don't be depressed
it's a story
you're out of protection
She's laying soup on ball
I teach
We're gonna act like gentlemen and the ladies talk
What are we saying though you understand he went to watch the TV at something his teeth
Do I got something in my teeth? We're talking about supines supines three-person supine
You got something in your tooth dude right there, you're gonna floss it out
Want to say hi to CB time
Why are you showing your teeth like that?
Why are you brushing your teeth with your nails?
Jody and ours
Yeah, punish it
And so now
golden girls trivia one question
One question like that
Gotty, I've never met someone who knows more about the golden girls than Jamie girl here. I mean it
He's more than Johnny's this guy, please do what you do Johnny. I'm famer
I got one question for you trivia Jamie. Jamie. I saw a clip with Bert Reynolds. You remember that episode with
Yeah, I'm gonna kick them. That's Blanche Sophia and Bert Reynolds were going to lunch
And then Bert Reynolds says which one Bert Reynolds said which was the whore and they all said me
Ask her a question though. Ask her the question
Ask her a tribute question
That's a good question.
What?
Oh, you know, last night, you're asking me.
Yeah, I forgot the last name.
Oh, that's a good question.
I am not.
Yo, Gotti.
Good shit, Gotti.
That's the first time.
All right, I got a question
All right, who did who did Quentin Tarantino dress up with the episode that he was in what did he dress up as?
the
I
Was in an episode of the golden nose. I'm one of them. Yeah, the trivia court the trivia question is what?
Who did he dress up as who did he dress up as in the
Sonny shit sunny
Elvis Presley
Type it in
Elvis Presley Quentin Tarantino golden girls. That's all you got
Oh the hotel shit
No, no, no, no, the golden palace palace golden palace. The other one. There's another one. There's another one. You guys actually know that the spinoff
You don't know it's called empty nest
Remember that don't show
They did a couple episodes with them in it, you know
Who's your favorite character,
buddy? Empty nest, holy shit.
Of what show?
Golden Girls.
of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of the four of
Yo, who is
How about this?
Who is younger?
Who is younger? Who is younger? Who is younger though? Sophia or Dorothy?
See this way with school about himself, but it's a hit or miss my man now
This is the difference between me and you Alex like I like to please women you see Jamie come up
What happened you were supposed to donate 5,000 dollars and you were hoping to jump out on that shit.
Jesus.
You're a Johnny.
Whatever a sweet whisper whatever like sexy things just learn them out. I'll soak it in
He can't even say it. Whatever sweet whispers like what the fuck are you talking about though?
Sweet nothing to my ear, bro
That's what I was talking about
Oh look at Mr. Trivia man. I'm sad all of a sudden
Trivia boy is pissed. Who's older? Blanche? Blanche? Shut the fuck up
Oh my god
You guys are funny
That's Alex, that's Alex
Hold on Alex
I like the nickname
What did he say? I was across the room
What did he say? Trivia Boy?
Jamie, what did he say? Trivia Boy?
Trivia Boy?
Yeah I was across the room
What did he say? Jamie, Jamie, hurry up and tell him
Okay, I want you to call me Trivia Boy
From now on, Jamie
Jamie, hurry up, what did he say?
What was the name of the dogs on Magnum PI?
What was the name of the dogs?
The dogs?
I was across the room.
Did he see Truby Boy?
I heard Truby Boy.
Yeah, I got two dogs, I remember the two dogs.
I don't know, freak.
I can't believe humans like this exist, man.
Strogan, he's strogan it, Alex.
Magnum PI.
I'll give you two more, Alex, and then
I'll give you a shot back personal.
Shut the fuck up.
But I'll give you two more.
I'll give you two more.
That's why I love Alex, but I'll give him two more until I actually start hitting him back first time
I have no idea where
Just get Joanie laughing. That's what Hannah will create. She does all kinds of crazy laughs.
I thought I was in a fucking fun house. I was like, what is it?
You know, you're in a fun house and you just see, who was that with Joanie?
Crazy, bro. Crazy mirrors with Joanie's fucking laugh.
I could only imagine.
Johnny what do we got boys or a shave?
What's on the road, Johnny
What would you rule Alex if there's grass on the field play ball that's it's fucked up
It's
You're a good house to do you Alex Alex and Joanie in a good
town though.
I hope she lives in a house.
Yeah, it's a haunted house, dick.
She doesn't live in a house, a haunted one.
It's a fucking wigwam.
the
Just the highlights of them because I fell asleep accidentally
Alex you are right though, I did get pretty little Johnny. I couldn't help it
She's in the depths of hell digs
Circles of hell the horrible it's a nightmare
Fucking I need help
Jamie what town stop it. I can't take it anymore
I think it was in Florida though
No, but like a special spot in Miami
That's why I thought it was like what is Jamie's Cowboys lives on Texas. Jamie's cowboy. Oh, Cali
Yeah
It's actually an echo sweatshirt that I had today so you're a Cali girl
Yeah, she's an Abercrombie and Fishmallow from Southern Cali, bro.
I'm not a model.
I just like that.
Serve up, dude.
You have a serve board?
You used to be.
Yeah.
No, no.
Do you serve?
Alex, do you remember the first time I met you?
That's so funny.
You never met me.
No, I don't, actually, because we never met.
Bro, you already are.
What the fuck are you talking about, bro?
I'm going to tell you.
I'm going to tell you what you said to me.
You're going to tell me what you said to me.
No, you know what I'm talking about on here. Oh, you mean on panel on panel. Yeah, you made me laugh though
Cuz do you know what you said to me, bro? You went crazy
It was me you know Katrina and you were like you sound like a fucking surfer, dude
Hang fucking 10 if you fuck with me, I'll chop off one of your toes and then you can only hang nine
Hang nine
Yeah, if you fuck me I'll chop off one of your toes and you can only hang nine
That's what he said he was like if you fuck with me I'll chop off your toe hang nine dude. I could have helped him
You told me the story about the dude tripping out running around, you know the meaning in the car the
And then I told you the story about the beach with the fucking yes
I don't think they want to hear that. Who the fuck is that going through?
No, you can't tell that story like it's because it's such a long story that like it doesn't know justice, right? To make it short.
No, it does do justice, but it should.
Is that me?
I don't know. Probably.
It's Gotti. He's got the speaker on it.
Joni has her TV on.
I got Peewee's big adventure on it
Oh, Peewee's big adventure on it
Oh, that's my favorite movie, big
That's my favorite movie, tell them not to watch that
A-Jing, A-Jing, Mr. Phone
A-Jing, Mr. Phone
Pee-wee's playhouse. Oh my god
What's the kid's name that they stole who stole a bite from was the kid's name
My movie saved all the animals there was a fire
with the pet store
Snakes and you just saved the whole store. He saved the whole fucking store
Oh my god, nobody's gonna call it in
Oh my god, he's gonna call it
He thinks that bike would go for now some no the best thing is famous at the end and he was watching the movie
Paging mr. Herman
That's my favorite part. You have a
Who directed the movie?
Who directed the movie
Michael King
that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it, that's it
Yeah
Johnny we shut the fuck up man. I'm trying to listen buddy. You know who Lou Reed is got me
You know who Lou Reed is he's a singer, right? Yeah, okay?
Take a walk on the wild side famous quote. That was his quote. Don't bore us
No, no, no Lou Reed. He's a singer like you said
Yeah
That's all right. Yeah, perfect. It's definitely a bit perfect days better than
You guys
The night cowboy you guys sound like a great
What's the song from midnight cowboy Willie Nelson sings that no no no no it's Harry Nielsen, but what's in this song?
I forgot how it goes Alexander. That's it. I'm putting you in time out
Like a rhinestone cowboy
Spank me baby
No, not like a rhinestone
It's a different song
Not that song
Show me whose voice baby
They just stole the bike
Rhinestone cowboy
Who's in a lap about it
Hey Francis
I stole my bike
I know you know this shit
I know Goddy knows this question
I know that
Goats are so cheap. Goats only two dollars. You don't even take two dollars to get up here.
What a cheapo. So much for that goat's over, huh?
What are you doing?
What happened? You said I'm gonna have to wait.
Yo, Joanie, you're a good time
Wait, is Ghost up here now?
Because he says some funny shit, and then you just laugh at that shit is funny
Another panel
Now he's trying to pretend that he's on this panel, but he's on two panels right now
He's got he's got two phones, so he's on one panel
You just got caught dick
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What it was you paid enough money kicked his asshole after he's on the other
Ghostie listen Alex you're gonna be a cake side. I think if he says one more
How about this ghost would you like to
Would you like to see this?
How is your erectile dysfunction going?
Is that one more thing you have been saying?
Bye-bye, you heard ghost.
Would you like that at least a pound?
So is that the truth, Alex?
If I ask about the erectile dysfunction...
Pick a boy!
He's on the other panel again, he keeps the fuck up.
Oh
Let's have a poll most annoying human on the panel
I'm gonna guess
That's my specialty, baby, I can't I can't deny it. That's my specialty
And the numbers go down I can't lie
I have to own up to it Alex
He's still on the erectile
Ghost doesn't like talk ghost doesn't like talking about it though in front of girls
Oh, oh, he is gonna talk about it. He said so how's it?
But but how's it been going though goes?
You see
Yeah, you already said you were gonna do it three times. I'm still fucking here
Listen the erectile dysfunction I got a pill for you. I got this guy's name is Dr. Jeff
I can get you this purple pill and it'll help it bro. You'll be good
Ghost don't get upset because they're laughing they're not laughing at you. They're laughing with you, bro
He laughed right you see he gets upset about he shit he does
I
Kid so funny when psych always says
Oh my god, oh, yeah, I've been seeing him. He's been drinking. He's been eating
Yeah, a lot Bickey lives with McDonald's breakfast lunch and dinner
It's McDonald's diet for the past few months my man. What do you mean a lot Liz good to see you?
Yeah, no kidding. It's just like does he own him? No feeling me y'all no scrambled eggs. No pancakes nothing
To cheeseburger meal number two
All day
Goes to come back boy, you don't have to get upset man
Please I'll be nice if you come back bro
Um, one word you're gonna be gone to talking there's dude
It's like the fifth time he said it now. I'm keeping the track. Let's see how high how many times he says it
Six time there it is
I don't fuck up. What happened? That's the prettiest girl that's you know deal with
this month. Everything. Oh, what happened? Keep talking. Keep talking. Keep talking.
Keep going guys. Keep going. Keep going. Keep going.
Okay, there's Duke
What the hell is that do we just get smacked around by ghost or something?
Would you like to do it again, would you like to try?
Yeah
Okay, you don't have a problem
Thank you, sir anybody
He gets a little upset when they're wrecked out
Doll comes up like you just got kicking me
Go
Why can't you overcome your fears ghost ghost you have to overcome your fear
You're scared of talking about your reptile dysfunction
Take your money if you can be honest about it
You ever P. We heard in the magic word that's what the ED is the magic words like P. We have its playoffs. Yeah, don't say it
I
Thank you for saying it
Yo, what about the jeep there's some asshole that lives down my block out
What about the five-year-old sunglasses
I
We got Harry nipples and a greyhound you understand what we do is
The I wonder if he makes do click is never any nipples
Rainbow bright sunglasses and a green home. Thanks. Hey, thanks
Yeah, that looks like a fucking
And then it's a great
Where's my
Jamie girl
Listen, don't I get excited when I talk about Jamie girl when I hear about I'm sure you know
Marine the car bro. She ain't got nothing on Jamie
They got
Jamie Jamie's like calling a lawyer right now. She's at the fucking courthouse getting a restraining order on Athens
They're gonna get excited about Jamie girl
Jamie's calling a lawyer
Alexander you're so fucking but you know what that guy other guys kind of funny too the two stereos with the naked man in the middle
So I'm not I'm not I'm not fucking doing YouTube terms of service
Yeah, but you and the dog actually look alike you guys look like twins
Which was the dog and which was the guy
Don't want the sunglasses the dog right either side of that man, so your stereo
oh that was pretty good actually is he making out with a dog now fuck bro you'll
say get up here is that ghost is that guy got pants on if you if you fucking
peace the alley going up on this is that ghost or is that the low down guy is that
low down
I'll go to center on here and I'll be making out with a gray
That's low down oh that's what LD stands for a low down. Yeah. Yeah
My dog
Sitting there at that pumpkin you should get one
I'll give you a big pumpkin
You should get one
You ever ride one
Hey, Johnny, I'm not here to make you laugh Johnny. So calm down. All right
That's not his purpose
Gotty you ever you ever drive your body. I don't work for these people
I like her too. She slapped you right back. She said I don't give a fuck what you said.
Well done Europe. We got a song. Psyche is giving blessing us with another gem.
Who's this to both of you? Don't hold it. They go like that.
I'm not saying he was there for you Alex to make a dumb song. At least we can do a listen to it.
This is Crystal.
Thank you. Into this song is done. Please read the animation with Alex in you. That shit is the best.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it's the greatest that animation.
That was so funny.
This course, I donated $30 for this shit, come on, bro.
By the way, God, I didn't forget your fucking ID, but you must have your ID on top of your
ID.
That's...
Oh, my God.
Not even I gave a dollar.
That's why.
That looks like James Cowboy.
Oh, that's Crystal...
Oh, that's Crystal Marie.
That's Joni.
That's Joni, bro.
That's Crystal.
That's Joni.
You see?
I think that's ghost
You know what, that's not a transvestite
Ghost is transvestite, face
No, no
I don't know
Hey, Gandhi, would you like to get away from my finger?
I don't know what you're saying, sir, boy
Hey, look at me, you're a baby
Did you hear that laugh? That was an AI
That was Johnny
Talk up to the show, look at the little actors, they're that icon here.
You're a year-latter, that's not part of the song.
In the back though.
Would you like your one?
He's still talking like he doesn't know what's gonna happen.
He's talking like he doesn't know what's gonna happen.
See, he's still just gone.
If that's what's gonna happen to life, it's all women's right, you see?
Alright.
Running back, bitch.
Fuck, I'm not in the winter for that.
Well, that was good.
Yeah, that was cozy, bro.
I like those titties, ghost.
Yeah, what's what happens?
Are they real? Is that AI?
You guys have no parameters.
You have no...
What? Oh, you can't do anything about it.
No, we got none. No parameters.
It's like making me fit her as well.
Turn the volume up.
I don't know what he's up to.
Big Joe says what the fuck he wants you to do.
Shut up, dude!
Hey, Big Joe says he'll be a fat boy.
So I can kick everybody.
You're just insane.
Whoop.
Big Joe says what the fuck he wants you to do.
Oh my God.
That's what you get.
I think everybody needs to be kicked for 15 seconds. Let's see you little shit
How much did he give how much did he give I'll double a thousand dollars I gave a double
Every time you kick somebody goes to prove that you got the little problem with your penis, you know
That's for 10 seconds. You need a
Everybody off the panel I'll double it right now
Yeah, take them off. Let's go
Got it was a you that months ago when you
Why fat boy, that's what you get. Hey, just don't me don't mean anything. I come on here alone
Oh Jamie come back.
I'm here.
How do you feel about that 10 seconds of silence?
How do you feel about a dumb dumb?
Why did you kick yourself?
You're so drunk you kicked yourself.
Did you hear him?
He was trying to speak but he was off.
He kicked himself off.
Can you hear me now dumb fuck?
I know because now you're back on.
Do you understand?
We could see your avatar.
You kicked yourself off you didn't mean to.
Shut the fuck up. You could never the best the best fucking t-shirt slogan is shut the fuck up ghost with an exclamation point the best
Just it just flows right out
Oh Sikey, you promised you were going to play the animation
Let the fuck up and listen, this is my song
I know, this is a good song, I heard it a couple times
From the Bronx to faulty in the bush
Will you fall in love with me, from the Bronx to fucking Psyche in the woods?
Paige, for the page.
And my P.D. Ron streamed the other day.
Next time we're on a trip, I love you
Look at Peggy, look at Peggy, she's...
What is she doing? Weegee or something?
Ha ha ha
Don't talk about it
They're not that dumb
No, but the point is that she laughs at your dumb jokes too
And I'm not just a funny one, because you love it
I'll ride the truck, you ride shot, gun free
The mixed malls tonight and city pride
City morning while you lay in bright
I'll keep the peace, we're proud
Together we'll tame each other's styles
Baby set me free
Page where you've fallen, love me
No, I'm saying how are you feeling though pain wise?
You mind when people ask you that or no some people don't like it when they
Tell you know this phone is too long
Yeah, it's terrible.
You're gonna have to fall in love with me!
I would simply just have to get out of this one.
Dude, shut the fuck up! You're just fucking jealous!
You don't got a song to take!
You little fuck!
I just don't got a song!
And if you fail, we'll have blown over some shit!
This is me in Pagesong!
Jamie and I don't need a song, bro.
Alex come back
They should have ended it with them together though, that would have been the best if they ended it up together
Wouldn't that be huge? Yeah. Yeah, like holding hands, you know what I mean?
I'm just glad that when sight made my song
It has it has summer and
Pages name in it and then the new one has yes good
Can't get anybody to shout out. I still think
Have you ever heard alex's song? Have you ever heard alex's song the first one that was written?
Yeah, that's still my favorite the one that the guy wrote. I forgot. Yeah, play it site site never played it on here
He's pussy the first one is the best cuz it's not wrong
It's like a minute and a half and it's it's funny as hell. It's 58 seconds long
It's called Alexander McQueen and white PD. Yeah, it's it's good
It's like you got to get happens one now, right?
Jamie not he doesn't deserve one. He would have one by now. I
Don't need one. Okay, but thanks, Jimmy girl
Alex don't want me to have
Holy shit, is that Johnny?
Johnny
What the fuck, Joni? You wearing a mask?
What happened to Joni? Where'd Joni go? You got rid of Joni?
I don't know, but her laugh was fucking crazy.
Joni, where'd you go Joni?
Yo, I can't believe you came up here, Jamie.
You don't usually hop up.
Joni, where'd you go?
I have been on for a long time.
Look at Lenore.
Yeah.
Oh, I want to go...
You ever see my cat you ever see my cat
It's so jealous Alex, it's all good
Just so what being a pussy you ever see my cat
Well, every time we speak you just keep it so often like it's all right, brother
That's how you know the haunts alive
I just mean any time it's like it would be it would make more sense. You know if you interrupt it, you know on a common
thing, but you just interrupt every fucking time
You ever see my car
Let's talk to Jamie. Let's just start talking about anything. What's two plus two Jamie?
What is it?
Uh, Scotty?
She got me boobin'
Enjoy the music and test the fuck up
So, she gotta turn up your microphone
Since we will not shut the fuck up ever
Like, by the way
For the rest of the night
What we're gonna hear is a dumb voice
Fair, that's fair, that's fair
That's fucking beautiful
Whose cake song is this?
Yo, game have you seen the picture of my cat?
Have you ever seen my cat?
Can you start with what's up?
I'm just trying to wind up Alex
Hey, check out this one on the hood of my car
Look how big he looks
I'm serious, I ain't even making fun of it. I love that fucking shit. That's good work
It's been a day for me to look at all of this.
Y'all know who I am.
All ghosts are getting upset now.
Nobody's watching this.
Yeah, he's getting pissed.
Daddy do you think he's pissed because we're talking on these videos?
Shut the fuck up asshole and listen to one song!
What a moron!
This guy does candy shit!
So listen to music!
That's crazy!
What are you guys doing?
Would you say some Alex?
Psyche plays a song and Nassan talks over it the whole song!
Who?
Like you hear this?
Can you see this?
Who produced this?
Like shut the fuck up bro!
Hey
Is that
that's Alex
Oh
What do you want to talk about anything you want brother let's run
Let's talk about let's talk about dum-dums. You know the lollipop
Okay, what is the mystery flavor what's what's the mystery flavor?
Dum-dum-dum who are you talking to bro? We don't know who you speaking to
Do you know what the mystery flavor from dum dum is you know the dum-dums lollipops
Right and he named himself like the dum-dum thing after the lollipops
We're trying to figure out the origin of mystery flavor. So what it is is
When they make a batch like let's say the first batch is root beer, okay?
What's left over in the root beer at the bottom of the barrel they use to the next flavor that they do
So if it's root beer and then cherry the mystery flavor for that would be root beer and cherry mix
and then they use the end
Yeah, they use the end of cherry with this next one. They're gonna do and that's the way they do mystery flavor
So I don't know there was a mystery flavor me neither. Yeah, it's the best flavor
It's the one with the question mark. It's the one with the question mark on it
I was a mystery flavor. It's fucking
I don't even know if you can find dum-dums around anymore. Well, they're always at the doctor's office. His name is T.I
Alex come back. I need Alex the numbers are gonna drop if he leaves
Well, what are they down to now? They must be down to like 10. I don't know but hey Alex always brings numbers Alex come back
31 well that one last and telling you
Oh Garrett, what's up Garrett Garrett's in the house. Yeah. Yeah, what do you say Garrett?
Good everybody a thing that is Darryl's here. I like getting under fucking Alex
of the hood on whose skin
Alex I love getting under his skin because it's not easy
That's your boy. You guys are from the same hood. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I love that
I love that but but but I like getting under his skin because it's not easy, you know
That's the whole thing with Alex when people get upset when he says shit
I'm trying to tell them like yo everything. He said he's just bullshitting like don't let it upset you
Everything he says is bullshit. I know
But he's good at it even before I have to admit I can't admit when I get pissed
I got pissed what he called me trivia boy, and then I laughed about it afterwards, but I couldn't help it
Good to see you though Gotti last time I seen you was that movie night you hopped in and hopped out real quick
Got it. Yeah, that movie. I will watch it. Yeah, I thought I was interrupted
He wants you weren't you weren't good movie though
Ah, that's a good one that would you know funny that movie phone. Yeah. Dubs was talking through the whole thing
Yeah, no, he was he was fine. I don't know what he was saying
He's a weird shit about Satan
Yeah, but he was talking about Satan's like wardrobe, but I was like what the fuck
It was either dubs of that dude cage, I think it was it was cage talking you right it was cage
You're true boy shut the fuck up
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Let's see. I bet you the numbers go up. Got it. Remember. We were at 30
Tank in a trivia boy. No one's they should be a little mouth faggot, but I can't admit everybody knows
Bro, you can't even talk you bro. You sound like you have a fucking air tank like a pile of
Waiter, what's wrong with you, bro? Can you breathe?
Assins every
Can't free you fucking every word you
Dying in front of her eyes, bro
Oh hang nine
That was so funny, but like I was like what the fuck that was the first time I met him, so I couldn't help a laugh
Lose I tried to argue with that
That's how much you so many dick you remember the first time we met
Remember that bro. You're pretty memorable. That's how much don't lose a y'all
I'm a loser. You are a loser on your present. I'm not going to deny it. I spit philosophy
Bro, you know what I mean?
What have you got? Hey, kid. You're a loser. You're bulls. You're bulls. You're bulls.
You're a little mustache.
You showed them. You showed them.
Summer, are you back in beta?
Summer or beta? Oh, I'm not getting involved in that. I don't know what the hell is going on there.
What happened?
Hi, JB. Hi, Ghost.
Hi.
Oh, what happened? What happened? I wave my little finger guess what happened? I know everyone
Yeah, that's what happened
So what's been happening over here? Guess what happened? I wave my fingers
What's going on panel
All of a sudden, we have eight people on the panel, but it's so much for like, I have nothing going on with my life, right?
Who said that? Who said you have nothing going on? Oh, everybody. That's okay.
Who just came up yet, Psyche? Who just came up?
um
Tell him psyche tell him Athens. It's Arthur just came up
We just came up psyche you say Mason bro, you're working Mason my man. I
Can't breathe Alex can be oxygen
No, all this cool
We were talking about
Windows he told me about the fucking shit that got down
What's the Microsoft shit that got closed down, you know how to talk to people not skype the other one
Nah, nah Microsoft's
Company that that was like Skype that didn't last I can't remember it. Oh
Yeah, you pointed that out to me it actually closed that day remember you were like it closed had its closing and it was that day
No, oh, is it skype? So what's the other one? Oh zoom you're right. It is
Do you ever shut the fuck up Athens
Hold your breath for two seconds, bro
The other time somebody talks about something and you can't handle it Alex. You just can't you know, we're talking about Skypins
Nobody steps up
Oh, he's gonna tell us every movie ever made. He's gonna tell us who produced it before Gotti sweet sweet
What sweet whispers is talking is all fucking damaged people too. Yeah, what the fuck is sweet whispers you motherfucker?
Can I guys can I ask like you just one question? Then I'll hop off. I don't know Alex might not let you go ahead
Thank you, may I ask you so I did the day Sam and was shooting on you
And I see that he has a wrench now
That's very confusing because you've said that if you're gonna be a mod here
You can't be talking shit about me and he constantly does so kind of
No, I have a thing like, you know, I have some mods that I am not necessarily like on the best terms with but
Hold on a second. Sorry. There's our content creators and because I would like to
Know if there's a real one in the fake one because there's fake Samans or fake other people
And so that's yeah, that's smart. That's smart. But you can always click on the channel and then verify it
Yeah
My mods like we were we have enough to our place. Yeah, but he's right
Author makes a better point psyche
Did you could you can always tell when you click on it and it goes back to the original channel?
I'm on stream your artist. I'm not in the I'm not in like the regular chat usually and so I can't do you have a second device
Do you have a second device?
These things fast. I just need to like be able to bring somebody up like I need to know if they're gonna form bomb
you're auditing the whole time.
So it's just easier.
They're both good points.
If they misuse it, I'll take it away.
But if they misuse it, I'll take it away.
But Otto makes a good point.
If you piss me off, then I'll take it away.
I agree with him.
Yeah, it's like a salmon is like, uh, yeah, he's being a jerk doing his bubble cocaine right now
With worst thing in the world, oh, I don't play roadblocks. Okay, you play fucking you Geo big difference
I'm not saying anything wrong with it. Yeah, not you Geo
He's just poking you, Psyche, does he?
Okay, Dottie has all the poking minds.
Funny as fuck, though.
Yo, you know how...
That's cool.
Yo, Psyche, I want to say something about you and Gotti.
When Gotti was talking to us...
It was like a month ago, and it was so funny, bro. You were like Bugatti. Do you like me? You like me, right?
Because I'm not making fun of you site. So just so you know, I'm telling you
I
right now if I count to 10 and you don't talk for 10 seconds 10 seconds
we go down to $100 can you shut the fuck up
take for 10 seconds
you stop talking you know that we got to get numbers
one
this guy's on the arrow
hell he he fucking takes an arrow like text by the way
he told me
This guy is on more pills than the pharmacy down the block
You see how
Like a kite my friends
Like a kite right now. Let's tell me out there when you want me to give him a low blow back. I'll let him I'll let him go
Let's go somewhere. I'm down to run one
You heard yeah, cool. I'm down to run one
Let's go sober after all
Finally page made it in the room finally
What I've been waiting three days to see this painting oh the tow pain
God, I got it. She showed a couple earlier tonight
She actually has like she showed other artwork before I've seen she actually
Hop up
You didn't show me
No, I didn't get nice here. Yeah, I'd like to shut the fuck up Alex
You over there shows paintings. Oh, it's not showing pains over here
the
that's what they did maybe we would have time for trivia is fucking
now we have to be just the only thing that is going to calm them down you understand
no honestly you don't want to calm me down
but we're going to listen to this moron talking shit for the rest of the night
morons you don't want to calm me down
this is both a trivia boat
Alex calm down do you know what will calm me down Alex
tell him Alex
the page comes up
hey gawdy
what
tell him Alex
don't let him talk to you like that
She can come up. Oh, poor ghost.
You want to come up, Alex? I want to put you on the stage.
He's got poor shit.
Yo, Alex doesn't fucking say shit
just because you try to get him to.
Alex will talk shit to me when he wants to.
Not because you're trying to...
He isn't going to come up while you're here.
Dick Page hates you.
She's not going to come up while you're here.
You're here ghostie though Alex. Are you gonna take that from him?
Yeah, why are you so scared of Alex ghost honestly
Oh
Now he's still collecting cuz he doesn't want me to whoop his ass. He's he's going after the ghost now
Well, let me handle it
Oh, she's coming up. Let me run one. Let's go sober
I'm gonna wait
She's coming up. Oh wait. Yeah, you're gonna leave you're gonna shut the fuck up. You're gonna be a good boy
You're gonna be a good boy though you want to go tumbling out of you
Keep talking
Are you a good boy?
Big Ghost
No, bro, because last time I a 12-inch cock popped up. I'm not I'm not falling for the
It could happen again goes for good try buddy good try I'm gonna get him
Before I die you will see those 30 feet I promise you
I'm finna put guarding on t-shirt. He's fucking with me. I'm finna pep that
I'm not poor mom in psycho an accident twice in a week
That was kind of funny
You don't want poor mom. Yeah, on accident
But twice, he's not gonna buy that one
I'm not poor mom in psycho
He's not gonna buy two turkeys and chocks, pulling up, you know, in one week
Yeah, I put you on a t-shirt, guys, but you'll need both
Yeah, good boy, you're a good boy
Bye-bye, good boy, bye-bye
Yeah, bye-bye, you're ass
Bye-bye, good boy
You've been a good boy. You've been a good boy. Bye. Bye
Yeah, you talk about you've been a good boy. Yeah, I have another drink
You know that will
Directile dysfunction if you stop drinking so much. That's true though. Well, what good is it? He doesn't do any
option
No, but he can't even do it when he's looking at that
I'm trying to be honest with him cuz he came clean with me the other day and had like an honest conversation about it
You imagine a girl comes up to him in a bar
Yeah
He'd say you being a good boy
You made a good boy you're being a you're being a good boy for me. That's right. You want to debate
You honey
That's the debate a good boy, you know what the fuck you're gonna do
You may be arguing trust me
Yes, sir, I don't know. We lost that thing stink. I'm not sure. Thank God
Now whoever has the power block man. I'm gonna miss out of the pain. I'm
Take advantage man
Let me pet this something
I'm pro poop. I don't give a fuck
What's the wrench ban them
If you're not propute, get the fuck out.
The mystery around the J-8,000 feet far from over, the Russian embassy has said that Russian
ambassador has read over the occupied Soviet area and taken the assassination of former
U.S. President John F. Kennedy to Washington.
U.S. Congresswoman Anna Polina Luna took to X to confirm this, following a 300-page document
She further added that the documents would be uploaded as soon as possible so that the American people have the control over the assets to them.
She would also claim that Congress attempted to obtain these files in the 1990s and was denied adding that assets to them.
What the fuck are you watching? I'd rather that assets back up. What is this history?
I'm running, I'm running, I'm running
while a host of theories did the documents released in later years suggest the general's reaction
was let me run one body that was a bad one way capital was